usgcn.com 2014-04-06

# Privacy Policy - AMERICAN JOINT

American joint International Investment Group, LLC, its affiliates and subsidiaries (together, "American joint International Investment Group" or "we" or "us") realize how important your privacy is to you, and are committed to ensuring that we keep your personal information secure. This privacy policy seeks to help you understand what information about you we may collect, how we collect it and how we may use and disclose it. It also sets out your rights and the procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

By using the website, you agree to the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your personal information, as well as to the use of cookies, as set out in this privacy policy. This privacy policy may be updated by us at any time and any changes will be effective once posted on the website. If we make any substantial changes to this privacy policy, we may place a notice on the website so that you are aware at all times of how your personal information is collected and used.

The Information We Collect About You and How We Use It

You are not required to provide any personal information on the website. However, you may choose to provide us with personal information, such as your name, employer/company, telephone number, address and email address, in order to request press kits and/or newsletters. We may use this personal information as part of our internal business operations or to send you communications, such as press kits and/or newsletters. We may also store your personal information and use it to market our services and/or for other purposes that may arise in our or your ordinary course of business.

We may also acquire your personal information in other circumstances, such as when you provide us with a business card. We may store such personal information and use it for general marketing purposes.

Disclosure and Transfer of Information

We will not transfer your personal information to any third parties other than where we share it with our agents, consultants, sub-contractors and service providers who assist us in running this website and our business and who are subject to security and confidentiality obligations. We may also disclose your personal information where required by applicable law, regulation or governmental request.

We operate internationally and, as such, your personal information may be shared with entities outside your home country, which may not be subject to data protection regulations as stringent as those in your home country. However, we require all such entities to ensure a level of data protection comparable to that in your home country.

Our Use of Information Collected Through Technology

We may collect information about you through technology such as cookies. Cookies are small files that a website stores on your computer to assist that website in tracing users and to recognise you if you return to that website. You are not obliged to accept cookies and, using the settings of your internet browser, you can choose to turn off all cookies or to be warned each time a website attempts to use a cookie. You can also choose to have all cookies deleted from your computer. If you choose to turn off or delete cookies, some services on our website may function differently or not function at all. By using this website and not using the settings of your internet browser to turn off cookies you will have consented to our use of cookies.

We may also collect your IP address for the purpose of monitoring website usage and calculating general statistics, such as the number of website visitors and the website pages that are visited. The statistics do not include information that could be used to identify any individual.

Risks of the Internet

While we use both technical and procedural methods to maintain security of the personal information we hold, please bear in mind that the transmission of information over the internet is not completely secure.

Links to Other Websites

This privacy policy does not concern any other website to which this website may link. You should review the privacy policies of any third-party websites to ensure you agree with their practices in relation to your personal information.

Your Rights

If any of the personal information you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address or you wish to stop receiving newsletters, please let us know via email at aem@usgcn.com.

You also have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you, to have any of your personal data deleted, to have any inaccurate information updated and to object to any way in which we process your data.
